





Summary

Jump to Section

Having 2.11 Years of Experience in supporting Applications using SQL Server Databases.

Good knowledge in RDBMS concepts and can construct a design relational databases model and implementation as per business needs.

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects | Work Authorization

Hands on Experience in Managing, Monitoring and Troubleshooting SQL Server 2005 and 2008 R2, 2012 Excellent skills in understanding business needs and providing technical solutions. Good inter-personal & communication skills.

Work Experience

- Interbiz Solutions LLP as Product Specialist -Application Support Sep 2018 to Till Date
 - ? We have implemented and support the Payroll Applications for both Desktop and cloud
 - ? Process payroll updates, adjustments, deductions and garnishments for employee record changes, leaves of absence, insurance coverage enrollments/changes, personnel/payroll status updates, swipe related, terminations and hires issued for payroll processing
 - ? Provide first line support for all payroll, Provident Fund and tax relates queries
 - ? Assist with the development of internal processes and procedures and provides input to ensure optimal HR service to the organization
 - ? Assist Employees, Management & HR with payroll inquires
- ? Work with payroll provider to address any pay related issues that have been identified that could include time entry, benefits, pay or deductions.
- ? Also had a good knowledge in Accrual, Activities implementation for both Inbound and Outbound process.
- ? Have good experience in writing procedures, cursors, functions, triggers, views.
- ? Good technical, logical, analytical skills to perform consistently with adaptability and 100% quality.
- ? Having experience in handling the Payroll Process in terms of weekly basis.
- ? Good Interpersonal, Communication and Presentation skills.
- ERetail Cybertech Pvt Ltd as Technical Support Engineer Jun 2017 to Sep 2018

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineering) from Tudinarashimareddy Engineering College, Hyderabad in 2013 PG: betch (cse) from Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University (JNTU) in 2013



Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

IT Skills

| Skill Name | Version | Last Used | Experience |
|-----------------------------------|------------|-----------|------------|
| SQL Server 2008 R2, 2012 and 2014 | 2008\$2014 | | |
| WINDOWS | | 2014 | |

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

| Language | Proficiency | Read | Write | Speak |
|----------|-------------|------|-------|-------|
| English | Expert | ✓ | ✓ | ✓ |
| Hindi | Proficient | ✓ | | ✓ |
| Telugu | Expert | ✓ | ✓ | ✓ |

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: 247 HRM

Client: InterBiz Solutions LLP Nature of Employment: Full Time Project Location: Hyderabad Role: Other

Duration: Sep 2018 - Till Date Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Team Size: 25

Skill Used: SQL SERVER 2008 and 2012, ISS, Application Support, Troubleshooting, Software Implementation, Technical Support, Weblogic, Javascript, Information Technology,

Role Description: Focused Implementation HR Professional with extensive experience delivering innovative solutions at the local and regional level. Expertise in employee relations, training, payroll and state laws with exceptional planning and implementation capabilit

Project Details: We have implement and support the Payroll Applications for both Desktop and cloud

Process payroll updates, adjustments, deductions and garnishments for employee record changes, leaves of absence, insurance coverage enrollments/changes, personnel/payroll status updates, swipe related, terminations and hires issued for payroll processing

Provide first line support for all payroll, Provident Fund and tax relates queries

Assist with the development of internal processes and procedures and provides input to ensure optimal HR service to the organization

Assist Employees, Management & HR with payroll inquires

Work with payroll provider to address any pay related issues that have been identified that could include time entry, benefits, payor deductions.

Project Title: Bigbasket.Com Client: ERetail Cybertech Pvt Ltd Nature of Employment: Full Time Role: Other

Duration: Jun 2017 - Sep 2018 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Team Size: 30

Skill Used: SQL SERVER 2008,2012 and 2014, ISS, Weblogic, Application Support, Software Implementation, Technical Support,

Role Description: Online shopping web sites for retail sales direct to consumers. Providing or participating in online marketplaces, which process third-party business-to-consumer or consumer-to-consumer sales.

Project Details: We have implementation and support for own application for Big basket online market

Assist With clients with directly or through online will give the support by 24by7. Business-to-business Marketing to prospective and established customers by e-mail or fax Engaging in launching new

products and services

. We will do the Testing for Android applications which are used for Big basket Picking process

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: OBC - Creamy Physically Challenged: No US Work Status: Authorized to Work in the US

Countries: United Kingdom Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.